adsfarm.co.uk 2015-12-28

# Cheapest classified ads Privacy Policy

## Privacy

Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

###  The Information We Collect: 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can put Ads and links to Your websites. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Website adress  
Email address   
Your IP address  

The Information We DONT Collect:

Credit/Debit Card Information 

###  The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

Information you provide to us to create a link is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the website. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

Exception from the above rule is your IP address. You can opt-in to display or not your contact email address.

###  Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

###  Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

###  How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by clicking the Edit link in your confirmation email received or sending us an email asking for support. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You are not allowed to modify your originating IP address and we will not do that for you.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take some steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

###  How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please[ contact us](http://www.adsfarm.co.uk/page/contact.html) at **info [at] adsfarm [dot] co [dot] uk**.
